<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sou Movie</string>

    <string name="terms_and_conditions">
    Welcome to SouMovie!\n\n

    By using this app, you agree to the following terms:\n\n

    <b>1. Eligibility</b>\n
       You must be at least 18 years old to use this application. By using SouMovie, you confirm that you meet this requirement.\n\n

    <b>2. User Responsibilities</b>\n
       You agree not to misuse the app in any way, including but not limited to attempting to gain unauthorized access, distributing malicious software, or engaging in illegal activities.\n\n

    <b>3. Privacy &amp; Data Collection</b>\n
       We collect user data in accordance with our Privacy Policy. By using SouMovie, you consent to the collection and processing of your data as outlined in the Privacy Policy.\n\n

    <b>4. Intellectual Property</b>\n
       All content, trademarks, and intellectual property displayed in the app remain the sole property of SouMovie and its licensors. Unauthorized distribution or reproduction is strictly prohibited.\n\n

    <b>5. Third-Party Services</b>\n
       SouMovie may integrate third-party services, including advertisements and external links. We are not responsible for the content or privacy policies of these services.\n\n

    <b>6. Termination</b>\n
       We reserve the right to terminate or restrict access to the app at any time without prior notice if a user violates these terms or engages in prohibited behavior.\n\n

    <b>7. Limitation of Liability</b>\n
    <b>7. Limitation of Liability</b>\n
       SouMovie is provided on an "as-is" basis. We do not guarantee uninterrupted service and are not liable for any damages arising from the use of the app.\n\n

    <b>8. Changes to Terms</b>\n
       We reserve the right to update these terms at any time. Continued use of the app after changes are made constitutes acceptance of the new terms.\n\n

    <b>9. Governing Law</b>\n
       These terms are governed by the laws of your jurisdiction. Any disputes will be resolved in accordance with local laws.\n\n

    If you have any questions regarding these terms, please contact us at support@soumovie.com.\n\n

    Thank you for using SouMovie!
</string>




</resources>